mixd.co.uk 2007-08-26

# Mixd™ - Creative Agency

Solution driven creativity

## Mixd consistently provides a creative, professional and timely design service.

* * *

### Privacy policy 

This web page describes Mixd's privacy policy guidelines regarding the collection and use of personal or corporate information that you provide to us.

This privacy policy was last updated on September 29th 2004. Mixd may modify the provisions of this privacy policy from time to time. The new provisions will be effective as soon as they are posted. Please check this page periodically to ensure that you are aware of any change.

**Types of information we gather and how we use it**  
Mixd collects information from users of its web site, potential clients, prospective employees, and alliance relationships to name a few, including the information you provide to us by submitting information to us through use of the site.

Mixd may keep track of this information and the information that you provide to us when you visit the site for our internal review, business development, research, marketing, and we store this information for the minimal amount of time necessary. We may also use this information to solicit e-mail for business development, research, marketing or promotional purposes or press inquiries. It is our practice to provide you with an opportunity to opt in for e-mail communications and remove yourself from this distribution list by sending us an e-mail to remove. We store this information in our database and do not plan to share it with third parties, except as described in this policy. If we ever need to share this information with other third parties, we will notify you. At any time you can remove your name and related information from our database, and we will provide you a choice to opt-out if you don't want your information used for any purpose or a particular purpose. You can review and update your information by contacting us at [privacy@mixd.co.uk](mailto:privacy@mixd.co.uk)

**Cookies**  
We use 'Cookies' in order to personalize your visit to our web site and enhance the experience by gaining a better understanding of your particular interests and customizing our pages for you. A cookie is a message given to a web browser by a web server and which is then stored by the browser in a text file. Each time the browser requests a page from the server this message is sent back which enables the user to be identified. We may use the information provided by cookies to analyze trends, administer the site, or for research and marketing purposes to help us better serve our clients. No information which personally identifies you will be collected through the cookies. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie so you have the chance to accept it and can set your browser to turn off cookies. No personally identifying information from you will be collected as part of these cookies.

**Links**  
The Mixd web site contains links to partners, clients, and other sites of interest to our users. Mixd does not control the privacy practices of these other sites. You should make sure that you know when you have left our web site and, if the web site you visit collects personal information, that you have read that site's privacy policy.

**Security**  
Mixd protects your personal information with several security measures. In addition to normal precautions such as physical security and firewalls, we have strict internal security policies.

**Children under 13**  
If you are under 13, please do not use this site.

**Information sharing and disclosure**  
Mixd does not provide information about you, except as set forth herein:

We may provide the information collected as stated herein to our business partners, which are under nondisclosure agreements with us not to disclose the information to anyone else, in order to assist us in growing our business with respect to similar products and services. If you do not want your information shared in this manner you will have a chance to opt out prior to collection.

We will provide the information collected in the event we are required to provide such information by a court, administrative or governmental order or subpoena or other legal process.

If we believe it is necessary to share your information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of Mixd's terms of use or as otherwise required by law we will provide the information collected.

In the event of a corporate reorganization, either by an operation of law, merger or purchase of assets, your information may be subject to a different privacy policy which we will make available on our web site.

**Privacy complaints**  
If you have any questions regarding this policy, believe that Mixd has not complied with the provisions of this privacy policy or you wish to remove your personal data from our records, please e-mail us at privacy@mixd.co.uk

**General**  
These are our current privacy policy guidelines that can be modified at any time by Mixd. This is not a contract.
